<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vaibhavi Bholane | The place where I express myself.</title>
    <description>Rants and random thoughts that come to my mind.</description>
    <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 21:57:24 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 21:57:24 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How and Why Businesses Use Social Media</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A new way of networking and marketing emerged with the advent of social media. Today, not just individuals but every company/business/startups/NGO irrespective of their size have social media presence on platforms like &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com&quot;&gt;Youtube&lt;/a&gt; etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-businesses-use-social-media&quot;&gt;How businesses use social media?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Promote their product/brand&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn about their customer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Address customer complaints&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Network with current or potential customers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use it as an internal portal where employee share fun moments of office with their colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-businesses-use-it&quot;&gt;Why businesses use it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;access-to-social-media&quot;&gt;Access to social media&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As per statistic, on an average a social media user spends about 50 min daily on Facebook, and spends more than 1.30 hr if other social media platforms are also taken into account. And with the smartphone and internet boom, this access to social media has become even more easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;user-data&quot;&gt;User data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social media platforms take the basic profile data such as name, email, birthday, location, job from the user. Users share everything they have in mind, their likes, dislike, favorite food, movie, actors, brands. Social media has the list of your friends, they know what websites you are browsing and for which product, what pages you like, what groups you engage in.
All the businesses want their advertisements to reach their target customers and not wasting their advertisement budget on non target markets. Social media leverages all the data they have to provide businesses the perfect tool to reach their target audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;user-attention&quot;&gt;User attention&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyday Unknowingly we are exposed to hundreds of advertisements through various media, but only a few of them are able to grab our attention. To win this race for user attention, advertiser has to use the best medium to reach out to us. It is said that we pay full attention while using social media which businesses can leverage to create &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brand_awareness&quot;&gt;brand awareness&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;low-cost-advertising&quot;&gt;Low cost advertising&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As compared to traditional advertising media such as Tv commercial, print media, big hoardings, social media advertisement is cheap and effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;word-of-mouth&quot;&gt;Word of Mouth&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Word_of_mouth&quot;&gt;Word of mouth&lt;/a&gt; is a free tool by which businesses can acquire new customers and social media is the best platform for this. Whenever an user shares or likes any post about the company, it in turn reaches out to his/her friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;creating-user-engagement&quot;&gt;Creating user engagement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Businesses try to engage customers with the brand by conducting competitions, informing them about new offers, discounts, new products/services/features.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs/how-and-why-businesses-use-social-media.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs/how-and-why-businesses-use-social-media.html</guid>
        
        <category>social-media</category>
        
        <category>data</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You and Your Social Data</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Social Media has become one of the integral part of our lives. Whenever you find some time spare, you quickly check your social media space created by Internet giants like &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, etc. Why do you do it? According to some psychologists, top reason people turn to social media is to get &lt;strong&gt;social acceptance&lt;/strong&gt; disguised under the name of &lt;strong&gt;entertainment&lt;/strong&gt;. Off late, accessing it has become more easier with the penetration of smartphones and Internet. As per data, in 2011 Facebook had &lt;strong&gt;109 million users in India&lt;/strong&gt;, this number now has proliferated to &lt;strong&gt;226 million&lt;/strong&gt; in 2017, i.e. showing a growth of around &lt;em&gt;108%&lt;/em&gt;. Smartphones ensures this number to grow at 10-15% YOY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the numbers mentioned above, you can imagine the amount and frequency of data being generated and shared everyday, and how important this data can get. We have become so habitual to social networks that with impulse we posts whatever comes to our mind, we share our current locations, the places we visit, the people we are accompanied with, what movie we watch, what restaurants we visit, what cuisine we like and what not. Some clickbait companies have mastered the way to extract this information from Internet giants (with your consent) and build their empires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-kind-of-data-is-collected&quot;&gt;What kind of data is collected?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever you sign up on to a social platform you generally never hesitate to provide basic information like name, email id, date of birth; Unknowingly you are giving away some very important information, using which Internet giants are piling up tonnes of money. Below I list some information that you are providing to social platforms:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;obviously-the-things-you-share&quot;&gt;Obviously the things you share&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since you are using a platform, the tings you do are obviously store in their database and they have all right to access, process and analyze it to their advantage. Some examples could be your posts, photos, tagged location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;behind-the-scenes&quot;&gt;Behind the scenes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platforms also tend to collect data that they can use to understand how you are using their services; so that they could do so called &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A/B_testing&quot;&gt;A/B Testing&lt;/a&gt;. Some examples here are the kind of data you view, hover upon, react and that engages you and the amount of time you spend on any/every section of the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;your-friend-circle&quot;&gt;Your friend circle&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the social platforms are “friend” oriented. Hence you tend to tag your friends in some of your post/image/event. This information seems meaningless from the top but deep inside this is used to create a huge gigantic graph/network that shows and represents the interaction depth of two people, relationship, strength of the bond and their &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Six_degrees_of_separation&quot;&gt;degree of seperation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;financial-data&quot;&gt;Financial Data&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some platforms also provide some kind of services which they charge for and ask you pay via Credit or Debit card, address and contact details. They save this information in their system so that you do not have to type information again and with this they say that they provide you better &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User_experience&quot;&gt;User Experience&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;device-information&quot;&gt;Device information&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As user can use any device to access any social media, the giants keep track of information like which device you last access their site from or browser you used and even location. This is done so that they could analyze, optimize and target a particular segment and find improvement hot spots in their systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-they-use-this-data&quot;&gt;How do they use this data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now comes the real question, how are they actually utilizing all of the above information. In this rat race of social media everyone is trying to be the best. There are several uses of the data they collect from you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;personalization-and-relevance&quot;&gt;Personalization and Relevance&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent past the most booming field and most hyped terminologies were &lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Personalization&lt;/strong&gt;; everybody was (is and are) doing it. Every company (small or huge) wants to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Personalization&quot;&gt;personalize&lt;/a&gt; user experience and show them &lt;a href=&quot;https://relevantor.wordpress.com/2012/02/02/what-is-relevant-content-anyway/&quot;&gt;relevant content&lt;/a&gt;. Right from &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.google.com&quot;&gt;Google News&lt;/a&gt;, to &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; feeds to &lt;a href=&quot;https://quora.com&quot;&gt;Quora&lt;/a&gt; answers, everything is tailor made - just for you. In order to implement personalization algorithms and make system smarter they need data; and hence they are collecting as much data as they can from the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;revenue-through-advertisements&quot;&gt;Revenue through Advertisements&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the Internet companies have “Advertisements” as their revenue stream. More relevant the ads are to the user, higher is the probability of user clicking on the ad and higher is the revenue. Hence system needs to be really smart about what sort of ads to be shows to a user. For this generally your past &lt;strong&gt;browsing history&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;activities&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;interactions&lt;/strong&gt; are taken into consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;share-your-data-with-other-applications-and-services&quot;&gt;Share your data with other applications and services&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet giants do not directly sell or share your data to other applications and services. But they do so by taking your consent before sharing it. This is done via &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OAuth&quot;&gt;OAuth (Login via Google/Facebook)&lt;/a&gt;. Social media companies share your public profile data to such third party websites/apps when you login to it using say Facebook/twitter or try to share some website data on Facebook. All such websites are of course obliged to get the permission of user to collect his/her photos, friends list, birthday, timeline posts, but it is always doubtful of how much is any user aware of such things before giving the permission to access his information. Social media companies have no control on how these third parties make use of such shared public data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;data-analytics&quot;&gt;Data Analytics&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Banks, credit card companies, retail shops, marketing companies, e-commerce firms use data analytics to their benefit. For e.g. Some credit card companies use your profile, posts, your friends profiles to decide whether to offer you a credit card or not. So in turn, it helps prevent frauds. Some other users of data analytics is target segmentation, anomaly detection, fraud detection and relevance and understanding consumer preferences and behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;can-the-data-be-misused&quot;&gt;Can the data be misused?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yes! Of course!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very well written article, written by &lt;a href=&quot;http://arpitbhayani.me&quot;&gt;Arpit&lt;/a&gt;, explains &lt;a href=&quot;http://arpitbhayani.me/blog/beware-of-which-indian-celebrity-do-you-look-like.html&quot;&gt;how facebook apps like “Which Indian Celebrity Do You Look Like” can misuse your data&lt;/a&gt;. I would explain it in a gist here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applications uses &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OAuth&quot;&gt;OAuth authentication&lt;/a&gt; (Login via Facebook) and takes your consent to extract and access some of your data through existing social media. Some of the data requested has nothing to do with the app but still it asks you for it. And Internet giant, since they have your consent, share it with them. Such application/websites may:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sell this data to some fraudulent entity which engages in sending spams or scams.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create fake profiles on different platforms and use it for illegal activities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Misuse your photos and data to blackmail someone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s world, using social media may be unavoidable, but one can be careful on what data they share publicly. With the impulse, one should not post any incriminating or illegal content, without understanding its ramifications. One should be careful before making any of personal data public. Social media data has been making life easier for users and businesses but this too has a flip side which can be avoided with more shrewd use.
write here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs/you-and-your-social-data.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs/you-and-your-social-data.html</guid>
        
        <category>social-media</category>
        
        <category>data</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All social-media articles</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment&quot;&gt;


    
&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/how-and-why-businesses-use-social-media.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;How and Why Businesses Use Social Media&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;A new method of networking and marketing emerged with the advent of social media. Today, not just individuals but every company/business/startups/NGO irrespective of their size have social media pr...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;




    
&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/you-and-your-social-data.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;You and Your Social Data&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;Social Media has become one of the integral part of our lives. Whenever you find some time spare, you quickly check your social media space created by Internet giants like Facebook, Twitter, Instag...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1979 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tag/social-media.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tag/social-media.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>tag</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All data articles</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment&quot;&gt;


    
&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/how-and-why-businesses-use-social-media.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;How and Why Businesses Use Social Media&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;A new method of networking and marketing emerged with the advent of social media. Today, not just individuals but every company/business/startups/NGO irrespective of their size have social media pr...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;




    
&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/you-and-your-social-data.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;You and Your Social Data&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;Social Media has become one of the integral part of our lives. Whenever you find some time spare, you quickly check your social media space created by Internet giants like Facebook, Twitter, Instag...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1979 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tag/data.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tag/data.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>tag</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All posts with tag</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a plain excerpt and of no use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;social-media&lt;br /&gt;data&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1979 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tags.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/tags.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disclaimer</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui column grid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic padded segment&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;ui header large&quot;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                This is a personal blog. Any views or opinions represented in this blog are personal and belong solely to the blog owner and do not represent those of people, institutions or organizations that the owner may or may not be associated with in professional or personal capacity, unless explicitly stated. Any views or opinions are not intended to malign any religion, ethnic group, club, organization, company, or individual.
            &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p&gt;
                All content provided on this blog is for informational purposes only. The owner of this blog makes no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site or found by following any link on this site. The owner will not be liable for any errors or omissions in this information nor for the availability of this information. The owner will not be liable for any losses, injuries, or damages from the display or use of this information.
            &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div class=&quot;ui header&quot;&gt;Downloadable Files&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Any downloadable file, including but not limited to pdfs, docs, jpegs, pngs, is provided at the user’s own risk. The owner will not be liable for any losses, injuries, or damages resulting from a corrupted or damaged file.
            &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div class=&quot;ui header&quot;&gt;Comments&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Comments are welcome. However, the blog owner reserves the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to this blog without notice due to

                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Comments deemed to be spam or questionable spam&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Comments including profanity&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Comments containing hate speech, credible threats, or direct attacks on an individual or group&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
                The blog owner is not responsible for the content in comments.
            &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;This policy is subject to change at anytime.&lt;/b&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1979 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/disclaimer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/disclaimer.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blogs</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui hidden divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/how-and-why-businesses-use-social-media.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;How and Why Businesses Use Social Media&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;A new method of networking and marketing emerged with the advent of social media. Today, not just individuals but every company/business/startups/NGO irrespective of their size have social media pr...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;article&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui basic segment left aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/blogs/you-and-your-social-data.html&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h3&gt;You and Your Social Data&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;Social Media has become one of the integral part of our lives. Whenever you find some time spare, you quickly check your social media space created by Internet giants like Facebook, Twitter, Instag...&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui horizontal list&quot;&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/social-media.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All social-media posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#social-media&lt;/a&gt;
        
          &lt;a href=&quot;/tag/data.html&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; data-content=&quot;All data posts&quot; data-variation=&quot;tiny&quot; data-position=&quot;bottom center&quot;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1979 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://vaibhavibholane.github.io/blogs.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
